# Pham Hoang Anh Nguyen

# Frontend Developer

■ anhnph.us@gmail.com

**\** 0493341674

💡 33 Ahern St, Labrador, QLD 4215

https://hoanganh31.github.io/anh-portfolio/

I have over 5 years of experience working with ecommerce websites for the biggest jewelry brand in Vietnam (PNJ company). Together with my team, I built new page functions and lots of promotion pages, discussed with the design team and the marketing team for the UI/UX. I believe that my experiences are suitable for the requirements your company needs. I hope to cooperate with your company.

## **Experience**

Web Developer .NET, Viettel Group
 Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

10/2014 - 07/2015

- This website allows school to management students, teachers and communicate with parents of student. Demonstrating the interaction between the school with teachers, teachers with students, the school + teachers width parents. My work made translate website and then made to build for new function or upgrade for available function.
- Website: http://smas.edu.vn

Developer, Nguyen Kim Company Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam 09/2015 - 02/2017

• Form 9/2015 to 12/2015

Position: PHP Developer

Make to upgrade for available function for Nguyen Kim website. This website of E-commerce use Cscart open source.

Website: http://www.nguyenkim.com/

• From 01/2016 to 02/2017 Position: HTML Developer

Project:

- 1/2015 - 3/2015: Super Sports Website

The website introduces a sport shop with its products and supports online order. Built layouts according to customer parameters using HTML, CSS3 and Js.

Website: http://supersportsvietnam.com/

- 3/2015 - 11/2015: Ecommerce B2S Website

This is an e-commerce website with full features to best serve the online shopping needs of customers: ordering, show products, carts, ... Built layouts according to customer parameters using HTML, CSS3 and Js.

Website: http://b2s.com.vn/

- 11/2015 – 2/2017: Upgrade New Layout Website Nguyen Kim

Implement as HTML, Css & JS according to available designs, cut shapes as well as extract color in accordance with design, make conversion, edit pages for new design such as product catalog, banner, Products, popup, services of Nguyen Kim, responsive mobile. Besides, during time work at Nguyen Kim, I create a lot of promotion pages follow Marketing design and plan.

### Frontend Developer, OneCorp Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

- Project: Build a new version for E-commerce website based on file design in accordance with user needs. This is online shopping website with many variety products such as: fashion clothes, footwear, stationery, functional foods,... Using Html, Css & Js to build these page
- · This company has gone bankrupt.

#### Front End Developer, Phu Nhuan Jewelry Joint Stock Company Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

06/2017 - 02/2023

- Project: Our team had built a new PNJ website from 2017 until now using open source Cs-cart. My
  duty is building templates for almost every page of the website such as homepage, detail product,
  checkout, category, and some functions related to frontend... Besides that, I build landing pages
  for promotion events. I support another team with problems like orders, stores, etc... Participation
  in building UI/UX for the website.
- Skill: HTML, Css(.less), Smarty PHP, Js
- Website: https://www.pnj.com.vn/

#### **Education**

#### Ho Chi Minh City University of Science - HCMUS

09/2014

Bachelor of Information Technology Engineer.

#### Skills

- Highly proficient creating HTML5 and CSS3, Responsive Web Designs
- Ability to use JQuery, Javascript
- Navicat tool (database management & design)
- Basic ReactJS, Bootstrap Framework

- GIT
- Agile environment
- Jira
- Less

# Languages

English

Vietnamese

#### **Hobbies**

- Traveling
- · Reading book
- Cooking